Erwin Chargaff Papers 1929-1992 Mss.B.C37
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1931-1992; 30 linear feet
  - Newman, Michael, 1981-1982 (Box 43)
  - Newton, Jack W., 1952 (Box 43)
  - Newton, Susan M., 1971 (Box 43)
  - Nicholas, John S., 1949-1950 (Box 43)
  - Nicholson, Hayden C., 1950 (Box 43)
  - Nickell, Louis G., 1957 (Box 43)
  - Nielsen, Jennifer Bronwen Kahn, 1967-1977 (Box 43)
  - Florence Nightingale Hospital (Box 43)
    See also Ser.IIb, Florence Nightingale
  - Nigon, V., 1961 (Box 43)
  - Martinus Nijhoff Publishers, 1980 (Box 43)
  - Nilsson, Inga Marie, 1955 (Box 43)
  - Nims, Leslie F., 1948 (Box 43)
  - Ning, Catherine Ke Chia, 1961 (Box 43)
  - Niroomand-Rad, Inan, 1979 (Box 43)
  - Nishida, Hiroshi, 1965 (Box 43)
  - Nishimura, Chiaki, 1958-1959, 1963 (Box 43)
  - Nitschmann, Hans, 1948-1961 (Box 43)
    See also Ser.I, Chimia
  - Nitsos, Tony, 1977 (Box 43)
  - Niv, Haggai, 1976 (Box 43)
  - Nobel Foundation, 1954-1956, 1971, 1984 (Box 43)
    Hammarsten, Einar
    Linderstrøm-Lang, Kaj Ulrik
  - Nojima, Shoshichi, 1958-1959 (Box 43)
  - Nolf, P., 1948-1949 (Box 43)
  - Norberg, Bo, 1957 (Box 43)
  - Nord, F.F., 1967-1972 (Box 43)
    See also Ser.I, Advances in Enzymology
    See also Ser.I, Carl Neuberg Medal Committee
  - W.W. Norton and Company, Inc., 1979 (Box 43)
  - Nouvelles Littéraires, 1965 (Box 43)
  - Novelli, G. David, 1950 (Box 43)
  - Novikoff, Alex B., 1951 (Box 43)
    See also Ser.I, American Society for Cell Biology
  - Nowacki, Werner, 1979 (Box 43)
  - Nowak, Suzanne, 1976 (Box 43)
  - The Nucleus, 1959 (Box 43)
  - Nurnberger, John I., 1955 (Box 43)
  - Nygaard, K.K., 1947 (Box 43)
  - Nyman, Melvin Anton, 1946-1949, 1954 (Box 43)
  - Oak Ridge National Laboratory (Box 43)
    See Ser.I, Union Carbide Corporation
  - Oberlin College, 1979-1980 (Box 43)
  - Obrecht, 1958 (Box 43)
  - O'Brien, J.R., 1956, 1958 (Box 43)
  - Ochoa, Severo, 1946-1974 (Box 43)
  - O'Connor, Basil, 1948 (Box 43)
  - Oeriu, Simion, 1957 (Box 43)
  - Ogata, Kikuo, 1957 (Box 43)
  - Ogden, Harold, 1970 (Box 43)
  - Ogston, A.G., 1952 (Box 43)
  - Ogur, Maurice, 1951, 1953 (Box 43)
  - Ogura, Joseph H., 1945 (Box 43)
  - Oke, O.L., 1967 (Box 43)
  - Oklahoma State University, 1965 (Box 43)
  - Okuhara, Eiji, 1959-1960 (Box 43)
    Rockefeller Foundation
  - Olby, Robert Cecil, 1967-1973; 10.0 Item(s) (Box 43)
    American Association for the Advancement of Science; Astbury, William Thomas; Biochemistry and organic chemistry; Editorial matters; History of biology, especially genetics; Requests for reprints; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.; Watson, James D.
  - Olinger, Chauncey G., 1972 (Box 43)
  - Olson, Kenneth B., 1943-1978 (Box 43)
  - Ommidwar, Kazem, 1950 (Box 43)
  - Omura, Hirohisa, 1961-1962 (Box 43)
  - Oparin, A.I., 1957, 1967 (Box 43)
    See also Ser.I, International Symposium on
  - Oravec, Michael, 1968 (Box 43)
  - Orekhovitch, V., 1959 (Box 43)
  - Oro, John, 1965 (Box 43)
  - Osawa, Syozo, 1953 (Box 44)
  - Osgood, Edwin E., 1955 (Box 44)
  - Ottesen, Martin, 1962 (Box 44)
  - Overberger, C.G., 1975 (Box 44)
  - Overend, W.G., 1951, 1954 (Box 44)
  - Oxford University, 1954 (Box 44)
  - Özand, Pinar, 1968 (Box 44)
  - Paabs Revista, 1971 (Box 44)
  - Pacault, A., 1967-1968 (Box 44)
  - Pacific Press Service, 1986 (Box 44)
  - Packard Instrument Company, Inc., 1963-1970 (Box 44)
  - Paerels, G.B., 1966 (Box 44)
  - Page, Ernest W., 1947 (Box 44)
  - Page, Irvine H., 1978, 1980 (Box 44)
    See also Ser.I, National Heart Institute
  - Pai, Anna C., 1980 (Box 44)
  - Pal, Bimal Chandra, 1962-1963 (Box 44)
  - Palade, George E., 1959 (Box 44)
  - Palay, Sanford L., 1957 (Box 44)
  - Palescandolo, Frank J., 1982 (Box 44)
  - Palmer, John W., 1945 (Box 44)
    See also Ser.I, E.R. Squibb and Sons
  - Pandey, N.K., 1974 (Box 44)
  - Pangborn, Mary C., 1942 (Box 44)
  - Panhans, Lothar, 1981 (Box 44)
  - Paoletti, C., 1962 (Box 44)
  - Papahadjopoulos, Demetrios, 1982 (Box 44)
  - Papandreou, Dora, 1954 (Box 44)
  - Paplauskas, Leonard P., 1976 (Box 44)
  - Pappenheimer, A.M., 1956 (Box 44)
  - Parenti, Franco, 1966 (Box 44)
  - Parihar, D.B., 1957 (Box 44)
  - Park, James T., 1949 (Box 44)
  - Parke, Davis and Company, 1935-1961 (Box 44)
    Pfiffner, Joseph J.
    Seegers, Walter H.
  - Parker, George, 1950 (Box 44)
  - Parkinson's Disease Information and Research Center, 1965 (Box 44)
  - Parpart, Arthur K., 1946-1947 (Box 44)
  - Partisan Review, 1960 (Box 44)
  - Passarge, Eberhard, 1974 (Box 44)
  - Pasternack, Richard, 1946 (Box 44)
  - Paul, John, 1959 (Box 44)
  - Pauling, Linus, 1945, 1953-1954, 1972; 10.0 Item(s) (Box 44)
    American Association for the Advancement of Science; Biochemistry and organic chemistry; Columbia University; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- Nobel Prize; Editorial matters; Requests for aid in finding positions
  - Pauza, Dave, 1975 (Box 44)
  - Pazur, John H., 1972 (Box 44)
  - Peacocke, A.R., 1952 (Box 44)
  - Pearlman, William H., 1957 (Box 44)
  - Pearman, John, 1952 (Box 44)
  - Pearson, Ann, 1955 (Box 44)
  - Pederson, Thoru, 1976 (Box 44)
  - Peeters, Hub., 1964-1965 (Box 44)
  - Pelargidis, Christopher G., 1965-1966 (Box 44)
  - Pène, Jacques J., 1964 (Box 44)
  - Penn, Nathar W., 1963-1976 (Box 44)
  - Pennell, S., 1948 (Box 44)
  - Peoples Business Commission, 1977, 1979 (Box 44)
  - Pepinsky, R., 1952 (Box 44)
  - Perez, L., 1983 (Box 44)
  - Perez-Mendez, Gladys, 1952 (Box 44)
  - Pérez Ríos, René E., 1977 (Box 44)
  - Pergamon Press Limited, 1959, 1961 (Box 44)
  - Perkin-Elmer Corporation, 1950-1952 (Box 44)
  - Perkowska, Ewa, 1957 (Box 44)
  - Permutit Company, 1945, 1953 (Box 44)
  - Perspectives in Biology and Medicine, 1972-1975 (Box 44)
  - Perutz, Max F., 1968 (Box 44)
    See also Ser.I, International Congress of
  - Peso, Osvaldo A., 1952 (Box 44)
  - Pestka, Sidney, 1976 (Box 44)
  - Peters, Rudolph A., 1952 (Box 44)
  - Peters, Theodore, Jr., 1974 (Box 44)
  - Petersen, George B., 1963-1967 (Box 44)
  - Peterson, W.H., 1949 (Box 44)
  - Pfeiffer, Raymond L., 1950 (Box 44)
  - Pfiffner, Joseph J., 1951 (Box 44)
    See also Ser.I, Parke, Davis and Company
  - Chas. Pfizer and Company, Inc., 1949, 1957 (Box 44)
  - Pfizer Therapeutic Institute, 1954 (Box 44)
  - Pharmacological Reviews, 1952 (Box 44)
    Eagle, Harry
  - Phi Lambda Upsilon, 1977 (Box 44)
  - Philip Morris Research Center, 1978 (Box 44)
  - Philipps, Georg R., 1960-1965 (Box 44)
  - Phillips, Gerald B., 1971 (Box 44)
  - Pick, J.M., 1978 (Box 44)
  - Pilgeram, Laurence O., 1953, 1955-1956 (Box 44)
  - Pilgram, H. Ira, 1971, 1974 (Box 44)
  - Pillsbury Mills, Inc., 1957 (Box 44)
  - Pin, Paul Joseph, 1953 (Box 45)
  - Pines, A. Leon, 1978 (Box 45)
  - Pinkham, Lawrence D., [196-] (Box 45)
  - Pinochet, Norbert, 1963-1964 (Box 45)
  - Pirani, Felix A.E., 1977 (Box 45)
  - Pirie, Antoinette, 1952 (Box 45)
  - Pirie, N.W., 1945-1983 (Box 45)
  - Pirk, Leo A., 1946 (Box 45)
  - Pirquet Society of Clinical Medicine, 1964 (Box 45)
  - Pitt-Rivers, Rosalind, 1952 (Box 45)
  - Pitts, Olin M., 1981 (Box 45)
  - Pivec, Ladislav, 1969 (Box 45)
  - Planta, Roelf J., 1961 (Box 45)
  - Plaut Research Laboratory, 1943 (Box 45)
  - Plaza de los Reyes, Mario, 1956 (Box 45)
  - Plehn, Jonathan, 1972 (Box 45)
  - Podgorny, Alexander A., 1977 (Box 45)
  - Poggendorff-Redaktion, 1964 (Box 45)
  - Pogo, Angel Oscar, 1958-1976 (Box 45)
    See also Ser.I, Hutner, S.H.
  - Pohle, F.V., 1979 (Box 45)
  - Poitras, Jean-Maurice, Jr., 1979 (Box 45)
  - Polacow, Ione, 1979 (Box 45)
  - Polak, M., 1954 (Box 45)
  - Polanyi, Michael, 1963 (Box 45)
  - Polin, Raymond, 1976 (Box 45)
  - Polish Academy of Sciences, 1961, 1975, 1978 (Box 45)
  - Polish Microbiological Society, 1952 (Box 45)
  - Politics Today, 1978 (Box 45)
  - Polli, Elio E. (Box 45)
    See Ser.I, International Society of
  - Pollister, Arthur W., 1950-1963 (Box 45)
  - Pollock, Martin R., 1962, 1970-1971 (Box 45)
  - Pomerat, Gerard R., 1959-1960 (Box 45)
  - Pontifica Academia Scientiarum, 1961-1962 (Box 45)
    See also Ser.III, The Problem of the Primary Structure of the Deoxyribonucleic Acids
  - Poole, H.K., 1974 (Box 45)
  - Poole, L.R., 1950-1951 (Box 45)
  - Posternak, 1950-1952 (Box 45)
  - Potter, Joseph L., 1950, 1952 (Box 45)
  - Powers, Samuel Ralph, Jr., 1944 (Box 45)
  - Prehm, Peter, 1979 (Box 45)
  - Preiss, Benjamin, 1981 (Box 45)
  - Prelog, V[ladimir], 1949 (Box 45)
  - Prescott, Blanche A., 1951 (Box 45)
  - Press, Frank, 1979 (Box 45)
  - Price, Charles C., 1962 (Box 45)
  - Price, Sylvia, 1985 (Box 45)
  - Price, Winston H., 1945 (Box 45)
  - Princeton University, 1976-1977 (Box 45)
  - Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences (Box 45)
    Beljanski, Mirko, 1971
    Braun, Armin C., 1971
    Hotchkiss, Rollin D., 1971
    See also Ser.I, Cavalieri, Liebe
    - Folder #1, 1962-1969 (Box 45)
    - Folder #2, 1970-1986 (Box 45)
  - Process and Instruments, 1953 (Box 45)
  - Project Survival, 1976 (Box 45)
  - Prokop, Barbara (Box 45)
    See Ser.I, Schneider, Barbara Prokop
  - Pronko, N.H., 1971, 1979 (Box 45)
  - Prusoff, William H., 1949 (Box 46)
  - Public Health Research Institute, 1947-1954, 1978-1986 (Box 46)
  - Pujari, Hrushi Kesh, 1959 (Box 46)
  - Purdue University, 1969 (Box 46)
  - Pyrocell Manufacturing Company, 1948-1949 (Box 46)
  - Quaker Oats Company, 1957 (Box 46)
  - Quarles, John, 1971 (Box 46)
  - Québec Science, 1979 (Box 46)
  - Quirk, William A. III, 1966 (Box 46)
  - Quivy, D., 1948 (Box 46)
  - Rábek, Vlastimil, 1949 (Box 46)
  - Rabinovich de Pirosky, Rosa, 1956 (Box 46)
  - Racker, Efraim, 1959 (Box 46)
  - Radin, Norman, 1945 (Box 46)
  - Radio Corporation of America, 1942 (Box 46)
  - The Radiochemical Centre, 1976 (Box 46)
  - Rajalakshmi, S., 1963 (Box 46)
  - Rajki, Sándor, 1966-1967, 1985 (Box 46)
  - Ralph, Ray, 1960 (Box 46)
  - Ramachander, G., 1961 (Box 46)
  - Randall, J.T., 1951-1953 (Box 46)
  - Random House, Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 46)
  - Ransom, Raemon Boam Seth, 1958 (Box 46)
  - Ranzi, Silvio, 1955-1956 (Box 46)
    American Association for the Advancement of Science
  - Rao, N. Ramakrishna, 1976 (Box 46)
  - Rao, P.V. Subba, 1960 (Box 46)
  - Rapkine, Louis, 1947 (Box 46)
  - Rapp, Bert A., 1972 (Box 46)
  - Rapp, Fred, 1976 (Box 46)
  - Rappleye, Willard C., 1964 (Box 46)
  - Rapport, Maurice M., 1947, 1953, 1986 (Box 46)
  - Rather, Roy L., 1976 (Box 46)
  - Rathgeb, Paul, 1950 (Box 46)
  - Ratner, Sarah, 1965 (Box 46)
  - Raut, Caroline, 1954 (Box 46)
  - Ravin, Arnold W., 1957-1958 (Box 46)
  - Rayle, David L., 1978 (Box 46)
    Wedberg, Hale L.
  - Raymond, Sandra, 1971 (Box 46)
  - Raytheon Manufacturing Company, 1955 (Box 46)
  - Reaume, S., 1949 (Box 46)
  - Rebman, Carole Ann, 1958, 1960 (Box 46)
  - Recher, Louis, 1961 (Box 46)
  - Redisch, Walter, 1983 (Box 46)
  - Reddi, Kutumba K., 1973 (Box 46)
  - Reddy, Sue, 1968 (Box 46)
  - Rédei, G.P., 1974 (Box 46)
  - Redner, Harry, 1980-1982 (Box 46)
  - Regan, James D., 1965-1966 (Box 46)
  - Regierungsrat, 1952 (Box 46)
  - Regueiro Varela, B., 1956 (Box 46)
  - Rehmat, Sheikh Javed, 1973, 1975 (Box 46)
  - Reichard, Peter, 1952-1953, 1957 (Box 46)
  - Reichstein, T., 1947-1954, 1964 (Box 46)
    Tamm, Christoph
  - Reid, Eric, 1953, 1960 (Box 46)
  - Reinwald, Karl, 1980 (Box 46)
  - Reio, Lembitu, 1951 (Box 46)
    See also Ser.I, Reio, Vera
  - Reio, Vera, 1950-1952 (Box 46)
    Reio, Lembitu
  - Reithel, Francis J., 1946 (Box 46)
  - Rejman, Ewa, 1964-1968 (Box 46)
  - Research and Forecasts, 1983 (Box 46)
  - Research Equipment and Service, 1952 (Box 46)
  - Research Equipment Corporation, 1952, 1955 (Box 46)
  - Research Society of America, 1966 (Box 46)
  - Research Specialties Company, 1961-1963 (Box 46)
  - Resinous Products and Chemical Company, 1945-1947 (Box 46)
  - Reverberi, Giuseppe, 1966-1985 (Box 46)
    See also Ser.I, Stazione Zoologica di Napoli
  - Reyerson, Lloyd H., 1964 (Box 46)
  - Rhoades, Marcus M., 1953 (Box 46)
  - Rich, Alexander, 1955 (Box 46)
  - Richard, Edgar, 1950, 1981 (Box 46)
  - Richter, Alan, 1965 (Box 46)
  - Richter, Robert, 1953-1954 (Box 46)
  - Richtmyer, Nelson T., 1959 (Box 46)
  - Riegel, E.D., 1971 (Box 46)
  - Rigas, Demetrios A., 1955 (Box 46)
  - Rinaldini, L.M., 1960 (Box 46)
  - Ritchie, A.E., 1955 (Box 46)
  - Rittel, Werner, 1954-1955 (Box 46)
  - Rittenberg, David, 1954-1966 (Box 46)
    Commonwealth Fund
    Merritt, H. Houston
    See also Ser.I, Barzun, Jacques
    See also Ser.I, Merritt, H. Houston
  - Ritterbush, Philip C., 1971 (Box 46)
  - Rizzoli, Carlo, 1952 (Box 46)
  - Robert, Leslie, [1964] (Box 47)
  - Roberts, Bruno R., 1948-1958 (Box 47)
  - Roberts, D.W.A., 1965 (Box 47)
  - Roberts, Daniel J., 1978 (Box 47)
  - Roberts, Henry S., Jr., 1949 (Box 47)
  - Roberts, Keith, 1985 (Box 47)
  - Roberts, Richard B., 1962 (Box 47)
  - Robinow, C.F., 1948-1951, 1958 (Box 47)
  - Robins, Eli, 1952 (Box 47)
  - Robinson, Donald S., 1952 (Box 47)
  - Robinson, Robert, 1952 (Box 47)
  - Roboz, Elizabeth, 1952 (Box 47)
  - Roche, Jean, 1949, 1964, 1967 (Box 47)
    See also Ser.I, Collège de France
  - Roche Organon, Inc., 1942-1943 (Box 47)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1947-1969, 1974 (Box 47)
    See also Ser.I, Okuhara, Eiji
    See also Ser.IIa, Rockefeller Foundation
  - Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research, 1953 (Box 47)
  - Rockefeller University Press (Box 47)
    Ehrenfeld, David W.
    Jordan, Helene J.
    Sapira, Joseph D.
    See also Ser.I, Ehrenfeld, David
    - Folder #1, 1976-May 1979 (Box 47)
    - Folder #2, Jun. 1979-1982 (Box 47)
  - Rodgers, Richard, 1969-1973 (Box 47)
  - Roe, Edna M.F., 1952 (Box 47)
  - Roepke, R.R., 1952 (Box 47)
  - Rohm and Haas Company, 1945, 1951-1953 (Box 47)
  - Roizès, Gérard, 1969 (Box 47)
  - Roosevelt Hospital (Box 47)
    - Folder #1, 1975-May 1977 (Box 47)
    - Folder #2, Jun. 1977-Jun. 1978 (Box 47)
    - Folder #3, Oct. 1978-1980 (Box 48)
    - Folder #4, 1981-1992 (Box 48)
  - Rosebury, Theodor, 1974-1976 (Box 48)
  - Roseman, Saul, 1960 (Box 48)
  - Rosen, Gloria U., 1950 (Box 48)
  - Rosen, Ora, 1981 (Box 48)
  - Rosenberg, Abraham, 1953-1961, 1974 (Box 48)
    Rouser, George
    See also Ser.IIa, New York Heart Association, Inc.
  - Rosenberg, Sheldon, 1951 (Box 48)
  - Rosenfeld, Louis, 1979 (Box 48)
  - Rosenkranz, Herbert S., 1964-1975 (Box 48)
  - Rosenthal, Albert J., 1981 (Box 48)
  - Rosoff, M., 1946 (Box 48)
  - Ross, Bertha, 1952 (Box 48)
  - Ross, David H., 1952 (Box 48)
  - Ross, Hyacinth, 1962 (Box 48)
  - Ross, Morris H., 1948 (Box 48)
  - Rossi, Bruno, 1969 (Box 48)
    National Academy of Sciences
  - Rossi-Bernardi, Luigi, 1971 (Box 48)
  - Rossi Fanelli, A., 1969 (Box 48)
  - Roth, Jay S., 1952 (Box 48)
  - Rothe, Adelaide, 1949 (Box 48)
  - Rothfeld, Karl, 1971 (Box 48)
  - Rothschild, Carl, 1970 (Box 48)
  - Rouleau, Suzanne, 1970 (Box 48)
  - Rouschias, George, 1978 (Box 48)
  - Rouser, George (Box 48)
    See Ser.I, Rosenberg, Abraham
  - Rowohlt Verlag, 1981 (Box 48)
  - Roychoudhury, Ranajit, 1972 (Box 48)
  - Rudkin, George O., Jr., 1947 (Box 48)
  - Rudner, Rivka Zelcer, 1958-1985 (Box 48)
    Karkas, John D.
    See also Ser.I, Morisawa, Seiji
  - O.C. Rudolph and Sons, 1958 (Box 48)
  - Rueff, Jacques, 1968 (Box 48)
  - Ruhland, Wilhelm, 1953, 1956 (Box 48)
  - Ruiz, Rogoberto, 1969 (Box 48)
  - Runnström, John, 1947-1954, 1961, 1971 (Box 48)
  - Rusch, Harold P., 1942, 1954 (Box 48)
  - Rushmer, Robert F., 1976 (Box 48)
  - Rüst, Peter, 1961, 1963-1964 (Box 48)
  - Rutgers University, 1952-1981 (Box 48)
  - Ryan, Ann M., 1972 (Box 48)
  - Ryan, Francis J., 1963 (Box 48)
  - Ryan, William F., 1965 (Box 48)
  - Ryan, William H., 1984 (Box 48)
  - Ryason, P.R., 1976 (Box 48)
  - Ruzicka, L., 1949-1954, 1961 (Box 48)
  - Sable, Henry Z., 1958 (Box 48)
  - Sacks, Jacob, 1946 (Box 48)
  - Sadowski, Tad, 1977 (Box 49)
  - Sadron, Charles, 1958-1959, 1964-1965 (Box 49)
  - Sadron, Geneviève, 1968 (Box 49)
  - Saev, G.K., 1957 (Box 49)
  - Sager, Ruth, 1961, 1964 (Box 49)
  - Saidel, Helen, 1945, 1949 (Box 49)
  - Saidel, Leo J., 1947 (Box 49)
  - Saito, Kunihiko, 1961 (Box 49)
  - Salanki, Janos, 1975 (Box 49)
  - Salk Institute for Biological Sciences, 1971 (Box 49)
  - Salomon, Michel, 1979 (Box 49)
  - Salum, José, 1959, 1961, 1964 (Box 49)
    some in Portuguese
  - Sambasivarao, K. (Box 49)
    See Ser.I, McCluer, Robert H.
  - Samorodin, Albert J., 1952 (Box 49)
  - Samuel, Rinna, 1963 (Box 49)
  - Samuels, Leo T., 1955 (Box 49)
  - Sanadi, D. Rao, 1953 (Box 49)
  - Sandberg, Avery A., 1962 (Box 49)
  - Sandler, Parke P., 1946 (Box 49)
  - Sandritter, W., 1952, 1972 (Box 49)
  - Sang, James H., 1964 (Box 49)
  - Santiago, Germán, 1974 (Box 49)
  - Sapira, Joseph D., 1979 (Box 49)
  - Sarant, George, 1971 (Box 49)
  - Sarett, Lewis H., 1967 (Box 49)
  - Saritsky, Louis, 1952 (Box 49)
  - Sarkar, N.K., 1956 (Box 49)
  - Sarkar, Pranab Kumar, 1960 (Box 49)
  - Sarma, D.S.R., 1963, 1972 (Box 49)
  - Saschek, William, 1963 (Box 49)
  - Sato, Richard T., 1950 (Box 49)
  - Saturday Review, 1963 (Box 49)
    Elsevier Publishing Company
    See also Ser.I, Elsevier Publishing Company
  - Saukkonen, Jussi J., 1956-1968 (Box 49)
  - Savan, Beth, 1982 (Box 49)
  - Savkovic, Nada, 1969 (Box 49)
  - Sax, Albert, 1985 (Box 49)
  - Sayre, Anne, 1975 (Box 49)
  - Scanu, A. (Box 49)
    See Ser.I, Tria, E.
  - Scarano, Eduardo, 1965-1970 (Box 49)
    See also Ser.I, International Laboratory of
  - Scatchard, George, 1944-1945 (Box 49)
  - Schacherl, R., 1979 (Box 49)
  - Schachman, Howard K., 1982 (Box 49)
  - Schapiro, Meyer, 1970 (Box 49)
  - Schatz, Albert, 1953, 1960 (Box 49)
  - Scheer-Schäzler, 1984 (Box 49)
  - Schein, Arnold H., 1953 (Box 49)
  - Schellman, John, 1980 (Box 49)
  - Schepartz, Abner I., 1949 (Box 49)
  - Schepp, William J., 1950 (Box 49)
  - Scheraga, Harold A., 1946, 1961 (Box 49)
  - Scherrer, René, 1963 (Box 49)
  - Scheu, Marian, 1953 (Box 49)
  - Schindler, Peter A., 1984 (Box 49)
  - Carl Schleicher and Schuell Company, 1944-1955 (Box 49)
  - Schlenk, Fritz, 1953-1955 (Box 49)
  - Schmid, Robert M., 1977 (Box 49)
  - Schmidt, B., 1969, 1971 (Box 49)
  - Schmidt, Gerhard, 1944-1976 (Box 49)
  - Schmidt, W.C., 1949 (Box 49)
  - Schmitt, Francis O., 1939-1945, 1982 (Box 49)
  - Schmitt, Harrison, 1980 (Box 49)
  - Schneider, Barbara Prokop, 1962-1964 (Box 49)
  - Schneider, Walter C., 1952 (Box 49)
  - Schnitzer, Robert J., 1943 (Box 49)
  - Schoeller, Ing. A., 1931 (Box 49)
  - Schopfer, W.H., 1948, 1952 (Box 49)
  - Schramm, G., 1958 (Box 49)
  - Schreck, Rona, 1973 (Box 49)
  - Schreil, Werner-Hans, 1966-1980 (Box 49)
    See also Ser.I, Ghiretti, Francesco
  - Schulman, Herbert Michael, 1955-1958, 1963 (Box 49)
  - Schurr, George M., 1979 (Box 49)
  - Schuster, Heinz, 1958-1960 (Box 49)
  - Schwartz, Daniel E., 1952 (Box 50)
  - Schwartz, Gerard P., 1943 (Box 50)
  - Schwartz, W., 1975 (Box 50)
  - Schwarz, Abby, 1976 (Box 50)
  - Schwarz, David R., 1965 (Box 50)
    See also Ser.I, Schwarz Laboratories, Inc.
  - Schwarz, Gerhart S., 1960-1976 (Box 50)
  - Schwarz, Henry P., 1951, 1961 (Box 50)
  - Schwarz Laboratories, Inc., 1951-1963 (Box 50)
    Schwarz, David R.
  - Schwarzkopf, Otto, [194-] (Box 50)
  - Schwarzkopf Microanalytical Laboratory, 1951, 1963 (Box 50)
  - Schwenk, Erwin, 1945-1946 (Box 50)
  - Science, 1944-1985 (Box 50)
    Abelson, Philip H.
    Granick, Sam
  - Science and Humanity, 1963-1964 (Box 50)
  - The Sciences, 1975-1977 (Box 50)
  - Scientific Glass Company, 1946 (Box 50)
  - Scolnick, Edward, 1971 (Box 50)
  - Scott, J.F., 1953 (Box 50)
  - Scottish Rite Committee on Research in Schizophrenia (Box 50)
    - Folder #1, 1955-1965 (Box 50)
    - Folder #2, 1966-1972 (Box 50)
  - Scudder, John, 1960 (Box 50)
  - The Seabury Press, Inc., 1976-1984 (Box 50)
    See also Ser.I, Herder and Herder
    See also Oversized, Doubleday and Company, Inc.
  - Seaman, G.V.F., 1968 (Box 50)
  - Seavy, M.J., 1942 (Box 50)
  - Sebek, Oldrich K., 1948, 1970-1973 (Box 50)
    Upjohn Company
  - Sebesta, Karel, 1961 (Box 50)
  - Seegers, Walter Henry, 1944, 1976-1979 (Box 50)
    See also Ser.I, Wayne State University
  - Segalle, Leo, 1961 (Box 50)
  - Seguin, Fernand, 1950 (Box 50)
  - Seibert, Florence B., 1944 (Box 50)
  - Seitz, Frederick (Box 50)
    See Ser.I, National Academy of Sciences
    See Ser.I, Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences
  - Semenza, Giorgio, 1955, 1981 (Box 50)
  - Sen, Mira, 1963 (Box 50)
  - Sendroy, Julius, Jr., 1950 (Box 50)
  - Senior Medical Consultants, 1975 (Box 50)
  - Sensini, Roland, 1985 (Box 50)
  - Serafini, Anthony, 1984 (Box 50)
  - Seton Hall University, 1964-1965 (Box 50)
  - Sevringhaus, Elmer L., 1946 (Box 50)
  - Sewell, William R., 1954 (Box 50)
  - Seymour, E.Y., 1948 (Box 50)
  - Shack, Joseph, 1952 (Box 50)
  - Shaheen, Edward, 1963-1964 (Box 50)
  - Shamin, A.N., 1982 (Box 51)
  - Shandon Scientific Company, 1950 (Box 51)
  - Shapiro, Herbert Simon, 1952-1977 (Box 51)
    Brawerman, George, 1957
    Horowitz, Jack, 1958
    Rosenberg, Abraham, 1956
    Saukkonen, Jussi J., 1958
    Szybalski, Waclaw
  - Shapiro, Robert, 1968 (Box 51)
  - Shapshak, Paul, 1972-1973 (Box 51)
  - Sharma, O.K., 1966-1967 (Box 51)
  - Sharp and Dohme, 1942-1943, 1951-1955 (Box 51)
    Barnes, Richard H.
  - Sharples Corporation, 1943, 1947 (Box 51)
  - Shay, Harry, 1946 (Box 51)
  - Shemin, David, 1959-1983 (Box 51)
    Kahng, H.
    See also Ser.I, Wu, Anna Fang
  - Shen, Blanche, 1963-1964 (Box 51)
  - Shepherd, George R., 1955 (Box 51)
  - Shettles, L.B., 1971 (Box 51)
  - Shibata, Kazuo, 1958 (Box 51)
  - Shifrin, Sidney, 1957 (Box 51)
  - Shigehara, Tatsuya, 1978 (Box 51)
  - Shigeura, Harold T., 1957-1977 (Box 51)
  - Shimazono, Norio, 1958 (Box 51)
  - Shimek, John Lyle, 1959 (Box 51)
  - Shimizu, H., 1951-1952 (Box 51)
  - Shinn, Roger L., 1974 (Box 51)
  - Shipley, T., 1971 (Box 51)
  - Shive, William, 1948 (Box 51)
  - Shortman, Ken, 1963 (Box 51)
  - Shostal, Walter L., 1981 (Box 51)
  - Shugar, D., 1952, 1958-1960 (Box 51)
  - Shulman, Sidney, 1949, 1955 (Box 51)
  - Shulton, Inc., 1959 (Box 51)
  - Shy, G. Milton, 1967 (Box 51)
  - Sibatani, Atuhiro, 1950 (Box 51)
  - Siddiqi, Obaid H., 1963 (Box 51)
  - Siegel, Bernard, 1955, 1958 (Box 51)
  - Siekevitz, Philip, 1973, 1978 (Box 51)
    See also Ser.I, Enzyme Club
  - Siew, Ernest L.C., 1970-1971 (Box 51)
  - Siew, Lieng Chen, 1970 (Box 51)
  - Sigler, Paul B., 1956 (Box 51)
  - Sigma Chemical Company, 1951-1975 (Box 51)
  - Sigma Xi, 1975-1984 (Box 51)
  - Signer, Rudolf, 1950-1952 (Box 51)
  - Siiteri, Pentti K., 1976 (Box 51)
  - Silsby, William S., Jr., 1956-1957 (Box 51)
  - Silverman, William A., 1979 (Box 51)
  - Simmons, Norman S., 1953 (Box 51)
  - Simon, Allen B., 1961 (Box 51)
  - Simon, Ernst, 1964 (Box 51)
  - Simon, John G., 1983 (Box 51)
  - Simon, S., 1958, 1968 (Box 51)
  - Simpson, George Gaylord, 1967 (Box 51)
  - Singer, Maxine, 1969 (Box 51)
  - Singh, B.U., 1970 (Box 51)
  - Singh, Madhav, 1968 (Box 51)
  - Singh, Pratap, 1973 (Box 51)
  - Singh, Rattan, 1965 (Box 51)
  - Singhal, Ram P., 1968 (Box 51)
  - Singher, Heron O., 1947, 1959 (Box 51)
  - Sinha, Ramesh Chandra, 1962 (Box 52)
  - Sinsheimer, Robert L., 1952-1976 (Box 52)
    See also Ser.I, Hartman, Philip E.
  - Sironval, C., 1964 (Box 52)
  - Sirsat, A.V., 1962 (Box 52)
  - Skinner, Dorothy M., 1967 (Box 52)
  - Skipski, Irene A. Lysloff, 1968 (Box 52)
  - Skipski, Wladimir P., 1956 (Box 52)
  - Skowronski, Christopher, 1966 (Box 52)
  - Skrabanek, Petr, 1985 (Box 52)
  - Slater, Donald W., 1959, 1971 (Box 52)
  - Sleeman, H. Kenneth, 1961 (Box 52)
  - Sloan, Lawrence W., 1952 (Box 52)
  - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research, 1948-1981 (Box 52)
  - Smadel, Joseph E., 1941 (Box 52)
    See also Ser.I, Army Medical School
  - Smellie, R.M.S. (Box 52)
    See Ser.I, Cohn, Waldo E.
  - Smith, David J., 1965-1966 (Box 52)